http://www.oceanologyinternational.com/en/privacy-and-cookies/

Visit
Why Visit?
Who will you meet?
What's On?
Travel & Accommodation
Oi Onsite Safety
Exhibit
Interested in Exhibiting?
Why Exhibit?
Exhibitor Package Upgrade
Stand Packages & Prices
Join a National Pavilion
Already Exhibiting?
Last updated: 13th May 2019
This cookie notice provides you with information about how Reed Exhibitions
uses "cookies", or, similar technologies, on our websites and applications
and other services (each, a "Service") to enable us to understand how you
interact with our products, to show personalised advertisements on our
website and other websites, to improve your experience, and to allow you to
use certain features, such as sharing content via social networks or other
communications channels.
This notice also provides information about how third parties may use such
technologies in association with the operation of our Services.
About this Cookie Notice
This cookie notice applies when you use any of our Services that refer or
link to this notice. This notice may be supplemented by additional cookie
notices, or terms provided on certain areas of the Service or during our
interactions with you.
With the exception to the cookies that are set by third parties,
Reed Exhibitions
that owns or administers the Service, as identified therein, is the primary
controller of your personal information provide to, or collected by or for,
the Service.
Use of Cookies By Reed Exhibitions
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites
that you visit. Cookies are widely used in order to make websites and
applications work, or work more efficiently, and help them remember certain
information about you, either for the duration of your visit (using a
"session" cookie) or for repeat visits (using a "persistent" cookie).
As detailed below, our use of cookies may involve the collection and use of
your information, such as IP addresses, or other online mobile identifiers.
For more information on our collection and use of this information please
refer to our Privacy Policy.
The categories of cookies used on this website are as follows:
Strictly necessary cookies:
These cookies do not store any directly identifiable information.
However, they are essential in order to enable you to move around the
website. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you
which amount to a request for service, such as setting your privacy
preferences, logging in or filling in forms. For example,
authentication and security cookies are used to identify and recognise
registered users and to enable them to gain access to requested content
or features.
Functionality cookies:
These cookies allow our websites to remember the choices you make and
your account preferences and to provide enhanced, more personal
features. These are set by us or by our third party providers whose
services we have added to our pages. For example, these cookies will
remember your log-in details. You can set your browser to block or
alert you about these cookies, but without these cookies, services you
have asked for cannot be provided.
Performance cookies:
These are analytics and research cookies that allow us to count visits
and measure traffic, so we can measure and improve the
performance of our site. They also help us to know which pages are the
most and least popular, and see how visitors move around the site. This
helps us to improve the way the website works and improve user
experience. All information collected through these cookies will be
processed in an aggregated and anonymous form. You can set your browser
to block or alert you about these cookies. Blocking these cookies will
not affect the service provided you.
1st and 3rd Party Targeting Cookies:
These cookies are set by us and our advertising partners to record your
visit to the website, the pages you have visited and the links you have
followed. We, and our advertising partners, will use this information
to make the website, and, the advertising displayed to you more
relevant to your interests. You can set your browser to block or alert
you about these cookies. Blocking these cookies will not affect the
service provided you, but will limit the targeted advertising that you
will see, or limit our ability to tailor the website experience to your
needs.
Social Media Cookies and Other Third Party Cookies:
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have
added to our websites that enable you to share our content with your
colleagues, friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your
browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests.
This may impact the content and messages that you see on other websites
that you visit. If you do not allow these cookies you may not be able
to use of see the social media sharing tools.
Flash Cookies:
These cookies are set to display video content using Adobe Flash
Player. Adobe uses Flash cookies to help improve your experience as a
user. Flash cookies are stored on your device in much the same way as
usual cookies, but they're managed differently by your browser.
Tracking Technologies Including Pixels, Script, Web Beacons/Gifs,
Page Tags:
These files, or, code may be included, either directly or from our
partners, on our website, in our emails, or, mobile apps to record how
you interact with us, to help us better analyse and improve our
services to you. They also help us understand whether you have visited
a partner website, aiding us to provide more relevant advertising to
you, as-well-as measuring the success of our advertising campaigns.
Tracking Via Mobile Apps:
When you use our mobile applications, we may record information unique
to you that are associated with your device (such as the device ID and
IP address), your activity within the App, and, your network location.
This information is used to measure and improve the performance of our
App, to help us to know elements are the most and least popular, and,
see how visitors move around the App itself. This helps us to improve
the way the App works and improve user experience.
How to refuse the use of cookies
You can prevent your browser from accepting certain cookies, have the
browser require your consent before a new cookie is placed in your browser,
or block cookies altogether by selecting the appropriate settings on your
browser privacy preferences menu.
The links below will help you find the settings for some common browsers
(please note that we are not responsible for the content of external
websites):
Opera
For all other browsers, or, for alternative advice, help may be sought by
visiting
www.allaboutcookies.org, or,
via your device user manual, or, online help files. For information on how
to opt-out of cookies set by our suppliers, please visit the applicable
links in the schedule as mentioned under 3.
If you wish to disable or delete a Flash cookie, see
Adobe Flash Player Global Storage Settings
(opens in a new window). Please note, disabling Flash cookies for Reed
Exhibitions may affect the services that we can provide, such as videos.
Third Party Web Advertising Services
Our Services may use Google Analytics, particularly within our marketing or
free content sites, for the purposes of analysing visitor / customer site
interactions including interactions with our online marketing campaigns.
For information about how Google processes the data collected please refer
to the
Google Privacy Policy.
You may opt-out of third party web advertising services that provide
personalised advertising based on your online activity. You can also
configure your web browser to delete and / or block the use of cookies for
any third party (see Section 4 for further information).
The following sites may be used to register your 3rd party opt-out
preferences:
click here or
here for the
U.S.
click here for Canada
click here for the EU
Please note:
Clicking the links above will redirect you to the appropriate third party
website. We are not responsible for the content of external websites.
Opting out of Advertising Cookies will not remove advertising from the
pages you visit; instead it means the ads you will see may not be matched
to your interests.
Changes
We will update this cookie notice from time to time. Any changes will be
posted on this page with an updated revision date. If we make any material
changes, we will provide notice through the Service or by other means.
Contact
If you have any questions, comments, complaints or requests concerning this
cookie notice or our processing of your information, please contact: Data
Protection Officer, Reed Exhibitions, Gateway House, 28 The Quadrant,
Richmond, Surrey TW9 1DN, United Kingdom,
dataprotection@reedexpo.com.
Where it applies, you may also lodge a complaint with the data protection
authority in the applicable jurisdiction.
Persistent
Bloom filter for detecting whether recommended content URLs have been seen before.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
ads/ga-audiences
AddThis
Session
Used by Google AdWords to re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitor 's online behaviour across websites.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
atuvs
AddThis
Session
Holds the ID of a visit (a group of related views), and a counter for the number of views in the visit so far.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
__atuvc
AddThis
13 months
User visitor count. AddThis collects information from visitors that does not directly identify an individual and is designed to identify the devices used by visitors.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
bt2
AddThis
256 days
User behavioural.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
loc
AddThis
90 days
Visitor location.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
mus
AddThis
13 months
Profile store status.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
ssc
AddThis
13 months
Service share consumption.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
ssh
AddThis
13 months
Service share history.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
sshs
AddThis
13 months
Service share history.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
uid
AddThis
13 months
User ID.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
um
AddThis
13 months
Partner mapping.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
uvc
AddThis
13 months
Visitor count.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
vc
AddThis
13 months
Number of views seen from user.
AddThis Privacy Policy Opt Out
ASP.NET_SessionId
Circdata
Until browser is closed
Used to maintain an anonymised user session by the server.
Circdata Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
_CEFT
Crazy Egg
1 year
Store page variants assigned to visitors for A/B performance testing.
Crazy Egg Cookie Policy Opt Out
_ceg.s
Crazy Egg
3 months
Crazy Egg – web analytics – track how visitors interact with pages on a site (performance).
Crazy Egg Cookie Policy Opt Out
_ceg.u
Crazy Egg
3 months
Crazy Egg – web analytics – track how visitors interact with pages on a site (performance).
Crazy Egg Cookie Policy Opt Out
_ceir, is_returning
Crazy Egg
5 years
Track whether a visitor has visited the site before.
Crazy Egg Cookie Policy Opt Out
GoogleAdServingTest
DoubleClick
Session
Used to register what ads have been displayed to the user.
DoubleClick Cookie Policy Opt Out
IDE
DoubleClick
1 year
Used to help us monitor the performance of our online advertisements. The cookie contains an ID that is used to identify an ad campaign to which a user was exposed previously; but no other data is stored by DoubleClick in the cookie, and none of the data is personally identifiable.
DoubleClick Cookie Policy Opt Out
ELOQUA, ELQSTATUS, visitor/v200/svrGP.aspx
Eloqua (Oracle)
2 years each
Eloqua employs cookies in order for its server to recognize a return visitor as a unique user. The cookies placed by the Eloqua server are readable only by Eloqua, and cookies cannot access, read or modify any other data on a computer. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.
act
Facebook
Session
Used to help track Analytics through session ID.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
c_user
Facebook
90 days
Used in conjunction with the xs cookie to authenticate your identity to Facebook.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
datr
Facebook
2 years
Identifies browsers for purposes of security and site integrity, including for account recovery, and identification of potentially compromised accounts.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
fr
Facebook
90 days
Facebook’s primary advertising cookie, used to deliver, measure, and improve the relevancy of ads.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
m_pixel_ratio
Facebook
Session
Used to optimize site performance for advertisers.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
presence
Facebook
Session
Used for site features and services, such as enabling a user to like, share and connect with our facebook page from our site.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
sb
Facebook
2 years
Identifies browser for login authentication purposes.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
wd
Facebook
Session
Used to optimize site performance for advertisers.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
xs
Facebook
90 days
Used in conjunction with the c_user cookie to authenticate your identity to Facebook.
Facebook Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
__cfduid
Feathr
1 year
Feathr cookie - tracks individual page visits to distinguish between users. This is used for remarketing, through display advertising.
Feathr Privacy Policy Manage your cookies
f_id
Feathr
1 year
Feathr cookie - tracks individual page visits to distinguish between users. This is used for remarketing, through display advertising.
Feathr Privacy Policy Manage your cookies
NID
Google
Persistent
The NID cookie contains a unique ID Google uses to remember your preferences and other information, such as your preferred language (e.g. English), how many search results you wish to have shown per page (e.g. 10 or 20), and whether or not you wish to have Google’s SafeSearch filter turned on.
Google Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
__utma
Google Analytics
2 years
Google Analytics© is an analytics solution, which provides information about your activity on an RX website. This cookie is used to determine unique visitors to an RX website. It is updated with each page view.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
__utmt
Google Analytics
10 minutes
Google Analytics cookie – used to throttle the request rate for this service; limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_ga
Google Analytics
2 years
Google Analytics cookie – used to distinguish unique users by assigning a randomly generated number to them.
Used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_gat_bu
Google Analytics
10 minutes
Google Analytics cookie – used to throttle the request rate for this service; limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_gid
Google Analytics
24 hours
Used to distinguish users.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_utmb
Google Analytics
30 minutes
This is another Google Analytics© cookie. It is used to establish a new user session with an RX website.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_utmc
Google Analytics
None
This is another Google Analytics© cookie. It determines whether or not a new session has been created.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_utmv
Google Analytics
2 years
Used to store visitor-level custom variable data. The cookie is updated with every page view.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_utmz
Google Analytics
6 months
This Google Analytics© cookie is used to identify how you arrived at the site, whether via a direct method, a referring link, a website search or a campaign, such as an advertisement or email link. It is updated with each page view.
Google Analytics Cookie Policy Opt Out
_dc_gtm_UA-#
Google Tag Manager
Session
Used to control the loading of the Google Analytics script tag.
Google Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
collect
google-analytics.com
Session
Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels.
Google Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
current_map
HotelMap
1 month
The most recent HotelMap visited, giving you quick access to what you want to see.
Your language choice, allowing us to personalise the experience with your default language.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
dmms
HotelMap
1 month
Registration analytics cookies set by HotelMap. The HotelMap registration identifier lets us show you deals that are relevant to your events and location.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
hmremote
HotelMap
2 months
Registration analytics cookies set by HotelMap. The HotelMap registration identifier lets us show you deals that are relevant to your events and location.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
ioe-data-id
HotelMap
8 weeks
Our HotelMap Analytics system uses cookies, log file data and embedded code to gather information regarding visitor activity on our platform, third party websites and other online services. The data gathered is used for analysis and reporting, to help improve the services it provides to its users.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
language
HotelMap
24 hours
The most recent HotelMap visited, giving you quick access to what you want to see.
Your language choice, allowing us to personalise the experience with your default language.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
offerLanguage
HotelMap
24 hours
The most recent HotelMap visited, giving you quick access to what you want to see.
Your language choice, allowing us to personalise the experience with your default language.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
wwhmid
HotelMap
1 month
HotelMap session identifier providing a seemless experience across our platform.
HotelMap Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
ApplicationGatewayAffinity
Lead Forensics
Session
Lead Forensics represents and warrants to Customer that its technology, including but not limited to the LF Tracker, does not capture or associate the data captured with any personally identifiable information. It does track and provide only the commercial IP address captured visiting the one of Customer’s Websites, the corresponding domain and contact details of the organization registered to such IP address, and the Website visitor’s operating system and browser type and version.
bcookie
LinkedIn
1 year
This cookie is used to track interactions with our Share buttons.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
BizoCustomSegments
LinkedIn
6 months
This cookie is used as part of LinkedIn Insights and ad tags to track visitors from our LinkedIn marketing.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
BizoData
LinkedIn
6 months
This cookie is used as part of LinkedIn Insights and ad tags to track visitors from our LinkedIn marketing.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
BizoID
LinkedIn
6 months
This cookie is used as part of LinkedIn Insights and ad tags to track visitors from our LinkedIn marketing.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
BizoUserMatchHistory
LinkedIn
6 months
This cookie is used as part of LinkedIn Insights and ad tags to track visitors from our LinkedIn marketing.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
bscookie
LinkedIn
1 year
This cookie is used to track interactions with our Share buttons.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
JSESSIONID
LinkedIn
Session
One of the LinkedIn cookies that are introduced by the LinkedIn social share button which are used to track which pages the user visits to collect them (cookies).
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
lFiidrsct
LinkedIn
Session
Used by the social networking service, LinkedIn, for tracking the use of embedded services.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
lidc
LinkedIn
1 day
This cookie is used to track interactions with our Share buttons.
LinkedIn Cookie Policy Opt Out
frontend
Magento
End of Session
Contains the End of Session ID during the ticket purchase and information on the preferred exhibitors on the website to suggest further interesting content after ticket purchase.
store
Magento
End of Session
Saves the active language and shop selection when purchasing an Online-Ticket.
.EPiServerLogin
Reed Exhibitions
Session
This cookie is set when you log into an RX website. It remembers that you are logged in, as you navigate through the site's pages.
[HOST]_trackingData
Reed Exhibitions
14 days
Similar to the campaigns.site.[THIS SITE] cookie, if you have arrived at an RX website via one of our marketing campaigns, this cookie stores the campaign's information and reports its success to us.
campaigns.site.[THIS SITE]
Reed Exhibitions
1 hour
If you have arrived at an RX website via one of our marketing campaigns, this cookie stores the campaign's information and reports its success to us.
novaState
Reed Exhibitions
Session
This cookie helps an RX website to remember your preferences. For example, if you view a site in a chosen language, every page within your session is then displayed in this language. As another example, if you add an exhibitor to your Show Planner, this is recorded by the cookie so that this exhibitor will be displayed in your planner, the next time you visit.
rxuk-recommended-exhibitors
Reed Exhibitions
6 months
Stores summary information on exhibitors that are recommended to a visitor
rxuk-recommended-products
Reed Exhibitions
6 months
Stores summary information on products that are recommended to a visitor
rxuk-recommended-sessions
Reed Exhibitions
6 months
Stores summary information on conference sessions that are recommended to a visitor
showcookiecompliance
Reed Exhibitions
Permanent
This cookie is set when you dismiss the "Privacy and Cookies" message, displayed at the bottom of an RX website. Once set, it ensures you will not be shown this message again.
url referrer
Reed Exhibitions
Session
If you have arrived at an RX website via one of our marketing campaigns, this cookie helps us report on the webpage from which you arrived.
voviciSurvey_invitationDateTime
Reed Exhibitions
60 minutes
This is another Vovici© cookie. It ensures that a survey is only served to you, after you have been on the site for more than two minutes.
voviciSurvey_noInvitations
Reed Exhibitions
10 years
Vovici© is the company used by RX to supply website surveys, often to elicit feedback on the websites themselves. This cookie remembers when you have completed a survey and prevents it from being served to you again.
webtolead.site.[THIS SITE]
Reed Exhibitions
1 Year
When you have: Submitted a request to attend, exhibit or advertise at an RX show OR Provided your details in order to access premium content on an RX site. This cookie remembers that you have already done so and ensures that you do not have to re-submit your request or re-enter your details.
__ncuid
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
_ga
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
_gid
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
ads_prefs
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
auth_token
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
csrf_same_site_set
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
ct0
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
dnt
Twitter
2 years
These are third party Twitter cookies. These cookies enable users, if they wish, to login to their Twitter account share content from our websites with their friends.
These cookies do not allow us access to your accounts or provide us with any confidential information relating to your accounts.
These cookies also allow a news feed of tweets to appear on the website.
Privacy Policy
eu_cn
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
guest_id
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
kdt
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
mbox
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
personalization_id
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
remember_checked_on
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
tfw_exp
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
twid
Twitter
2 years
These cookies enable us to track visitor activity from our Twitter ads on our website, and also to allow users to share content from our websites. They cookies do not provide us with any confidential information relating to your account.
Twitter Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_combi
Visual Website Opitmiser
100 days
This cookie is generated when users reach a particular combination. This cookie ensures that users see the same variation that they saw on their previous visit to the page.
VWO Cookie Policy Opt Out
_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_goal_GOAL_ID
Visual Website Opitmiser
100 days
This cookie is generated when a goal is created.
VWO Cookie Policy Opt Out
_vis_opt_test_cookie
Visual Website Opitmiser
10 years
This is a temporary session cookie generated to detect if the cookies are enabled on the user browser or not.
VWO Cookie Policy Opt Out
_vwo_uuid_v2
Visual Website Opitmiser
100 days
This cookie generates a unique ID for every visitor and is used for the report segmentation feature in VWO. It also allows you to view data in a more refined manner. If you have a test running on multiple domains, you will notice test-specific UUID values.
VWO Cookie Policy Opt Out
_vwo_uuid
Visual Website Optimiser
100 days
This cookie generates a unique ID for every visitor and is used for the report segmentation feature in VWO. It also allows you to view data in a more refined manner. If you have a test running on multiple domains, you will notice test-specific UUID values.
VWO Cookie Policy Opt Out
WalkMe cookies - Full cookie list
WalkMe
Various
WalkMe cookies do not collect end-user or website information, only WalkMe related content. Browser storage is used to manage its own state and data.
WalkMe Privacy Policy Manage your cookies
wfvt_#
Wordfence
Session
Wordfence uses cookies: To uniquely identify visitors shown in Wordfence Live traffic and to identify if a user has visited a unique page you’ve set to allow them to bypass country blocking so that country-blocking does not prevent them from viewing the site.
Wordfence Privacy Policy Manage your cookies
wordfence_verifiedHuman
Wordfence
Session
Wordfence uses cookies: To uniquely identify visitors shown in Wordfence Live traffic and to identify if a user has visited a unique page you’ve set to allow them to bypass country blocking so that country-blocking does not prevent them from viewing the site.
Wordfence Privacy Policy Manage your cookies
PHPSESSID
www.123formbuilder.com
Session
Maintains inputted data in case of errors on submit or if page refreshed.
123FB Cookie Policy Manage your cookies
In partnership with
Endorsing Associations
Show dates & location
Tue 1 December 2020 09:00-19:00
Wed 2 December 2020 09:00-18:00
Thu 3 December 2020 09:00-17:00
Excel London,
1 Western Gateway,
Royal Victoria Dock,
London Docklands,
E16 1XL
Useful links
About
Why visit?
Oi Connect
Need help?
Cookie Settings
Coronavirus updates
Contact us
Live Help - Online
Live Help - Offline
Contact us
+44 (0)20 82712133
Meet the Team
Organised by
©
Reed Exhibitions Ltd.
REED EXHIBITIONS LIMITED is a private limited company, having its registered and principal office at Gateway House, 28 The Quadrant, Richmond, Surrey, TW9 1ON, registered in England and Wales with Company No. 678540.
Business activity: Activities of exhibition and fair organisers
VAT No. GB 232 4004 20
Tax ID No: 13960 00581.
OI Oceanology International is a registered trade mark of Reed Exhibitions Limited
